Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- ♪ See these eyes of green ♪
♪ I can stare
for a thousand years ♪
♪ Colder than the moon ♪
♪ Well. it's been so long ♪
♪ And I've been
putting out fire ♪
♪ With gasoline ♪
♪ See these eyes of red ♪
♪ Red like jungle
burning bright ♪
♪ Those who feel me near ♪
♪ Pull the blinds
and change their mind ♪
♪ It's been so long ♪
♪ Well. it's been so long ♪
♪ I've been putting out fire
with gasoline ♪
♪ Putting out fire ♪
♪ See these tears of blue ♪
♪ An ageless heart
that can never mend ♪
♪ Tears can never dry ♪
♪ A judgment made ♪
♪ Can never bend ♪
♪ See these eyes so green ♪
♪ I can stare
for a thousand years ♪
♪ Just be still with me ♪
♪ You wouldn't believe
what I've been through ♪
♪ Well. it's been so long ♪
♪ It's been so long ♪
♪ And I've been putting out fire
with gasoline ♪
♪ Putting out fire ♪
♪ With gasoline ♪
-♪ 'Cause if you don't know me
well ♪
♪ You had better listen ♪
♪ To the facts about me. baby ♪
♪ That you better know ♪
♪ I'm not one of you ♪
♪ You're not one of me ♪
♪ And the things I see ♪
♪ You may not see ♪
♪ Like. pick up the beat ♪
♪ And close the hand ♪
♪ Check me out. baby ♪
♪ I'm the Mix Match Man ♪
♪ The Mix Match Man ♪
-Found it.
Found it.
-Miller.
-♪ When I wake up
in the morning. love ♪
♪ And the sunlight hurts
my eyes ♪
♪ And something
without warning. love ♪
♪ Bears heavy on my mind ♪
♪ Then I look at you ♪
♪ And the world's all right
with me ♪
♪ Just one look at you ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna be ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
-♪ Lovely day. lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day. lovely day ♪
-♪ A lovely day ♪
-♪ Lovely day. lovely day.
lovely day. lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day. lovely day.
-♪ When the day
that lies ahead of me ♪
♪ Seems impossible to face ♪
♪ When someone else
instead of me ♪
♪ Always seems to know the way ♪
♪ Then I look at you ♪
♪ And the world's all right
with me ♪
♪ Ah. just want one look
at you ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna be ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
Yeah.
-Yeah?
Yeah!
Yes!
Oh!
-♪ Listen to the wind blow ♪
♪ Watch the sun rise ♪
♪ Run in the shadows ♪
♪ Damn your love.
damn your lies ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now ♪
♪ You will never love me again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now ♪
-♪ You don't love me now ♪
-♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
♪ Listen to the wind blow ♪
♪ Down comes the night ♪
♪ Run in the shadows ♪
♪ Damn your love.
damn your lies ♪
♪ Break the silence ♪
♪ Damn the dark.
damn the light ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now ♪
♪ You will never love me again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now ♪
-♪ You don't love me now ♪
-♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
-♪ And if you don't love me
now ♪
-♪ You don't love me now ♪
-♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying ♪
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
-♪ Never break the chain ♪
♪ Chains ♪
♪ Keep us together ♪
-♪ Running in the shadows ♪
-♪ Chains ♪
♪ Keep us together ♪
-♪ Running in the shadows ♪
-♪ Chains ♪
♪ Keep us together ♪
-♪ Running in the shadows ♪
- ♪ Chains ♪
- I loved you!
I loved you!
-♪ To get off. to get off ♪
♪ To get off. to get off ♪
♪ To get off. to get. get off ♪
♪ Looking through that dress
drive me crazy and makes me ♪
-♪ Get off ♪
♪ Sensuality excites my mind.
it makes me ♪
♪ Get off ♪
-♪ If I were you. I'd get
a good perspective on how to ♪
♪ Get off ♪
-Don't fucking touch me.
-Hey.
-♪ Love me wild ♪
-Ow! Fucker!
-♪ Get off ♪
-♪ Tie me up at your place.
I can love you crazy ♪
♪ In the heat.
you will understand ♪
♪ Danger and excitement.
that's what makes a lady ♪
♪ Find out what she wants
in a man ♪
♪ To get off. to get off ♪
-Let's go.
-♪ To get off. to get off ♪
♪ To get off ♪
-Ow!
-♪ To get off ♪
-gtt
-♪ Ooh-ooh! Ooh-ooh!
Ooh-ooh! Ooh-ooh! ♪
-Fuck you!
Stop!
- Yeah!
♪ Get off ♪
-Aah! Aah!
-♪ Doing all right ♪
♪ A little jiving
on a Saturday night ♪
♪ And come what may ♪
♪ Gonna dance the day away ♪
♪ Jenny was sweet ♪
♪ She always smiled
for the people she'd meet ♪
♪ On trouble and strife ♪
♪ She had another way
of looking at life ♪
♪ The news is blue ♪
-♪ The news is blue ♪
-♪ It has its own way
to get to you ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
-♪ What can I do? ♪
-♪ I'll never remember
my time with you ♪
♪ Pick up your feet ♪
♪ Got to move to the trick
of the beat ♪
♪ There is no elite ♪
♪ Just take your place
in the driver's seat ♪
-♪ Driver's seat ♪
♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
♪ Driver's seat ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ We're doing all right ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
-♪ A little jiving
on a Saturday night ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ And come what may ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
-♪ Gonna dance the day away ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ Driver's seat ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
- ♪ Driver's seat ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ Jenny was sweet ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
- ♪ There is no elite ♪
♪ You got to see I got to go ♪
♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ That would be a lie ♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪ I wasn't trying
to keep you down ♪
♪ But I'd like
to keep you around ♪
♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪ And you can take me
for a ride ♪
♪ But if you want me.
just lay low ♪
♪ And make me stay
when I should go ♪
♪ I might not talk.
but still you try ♪
♪ Because it's in me.
we know ♪
♪ And you know ♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪ So you can take me
for a ride ♪
♪ But if you want me.
just lay low ♪
♪ And make me stay... ♪
-Hello.
-♪ ...when I should go ♪
-Hi.
-♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's so good. it's so good.
it's so good ♪
♪ It's so good. it's so good ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Heaven knows. heaven knows.
heaven knows ♪
♪ Heaven knows. heaven knows ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I feel love. I feel love.
I feel love ♪
♪ I feel love. I feel love ♪
♪ I feel love ♪
-♪ ...joy ♪
-♪ Gonna have
a merry Christmas ♪
♪ It'll be the real McCoy ♪
♪ We've got things to prepare ♪
♪ Let there be loving ♪
♪ Let us care ♪
♪ Gonna be a merry Christmas
with magic in the air ♪
-♪ We can meet
under the mistletoe ♪
-♪ Doo-wa. doo-wa. ooh-wa ♪
-♪ And we can always hope
there might be snow. oh. oh ♪
♪ Santa Claus is on his way ♪
♪ So prepare for Christmas Day ♪
♪ Let's have a merry Christmas ♪
-Want to mind your own business?
Huh?
Merry fuckin' Christmas.
-♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
toll loud and long ♪
♪ Your message sweet
heal and prolong ♪
♪ Come. all you people.
join in the singing ♪
♪ Repeat the story
told by the ringing ♪
♪ Ring. ring. ring. ring ♪
♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
throughout the earth ♪
♪ Tell of the news
of Jesus' birth ♪
-♪ Loudly proclaim
with one accord ♪
♪ The happy tale ♪
♪ Welcome the Lord ♪
-♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
-♪ Ring ♪
♪ Ring Christmas bells.
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
♪ Loudly proclaim
with one accord ♪
♪ The happy tale ♪
♪ Welcome the Lord ♪
♪ Ring. Christmas bells.
sound far and near ♪
♪ The birthday of Jesus
is here ♪
-♪ Herald the news
to old and young ♪
♪ Tell it to all
in every tongue ♪
♪ Ring. ring. ring. ring ♪
♪ Ring ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
-Yo.
Fuck off. man.
Oh!
-♪ The wind blew some luck
in my direction ♪
♪ I caught it in my hands
today ♪
♪ I finally made
a tricky French connection ♪
♪ You winked and gave me
your okay ♪
♪ I'll take you on a trip
beside the ocean ♪
♪ And drop the top
at Chesapeake Bay ♪
-♪ Ain't nothing like
a scattered dose of ocean ♪
♪ The moon will send you
on your way ♪
♪ Moonlight ♪
♪ Feels right ♪
♪ We'll lay back and observe
the constellations ♪
♪ And watch the moon
smiling bright ♪
♪ I'll play the radio
on Southern stations ♪
♪ 'Cause Southern belles
are hell at night ♪
♪ You say you came to Baltimore
from Ole Miss ♪
♪ A class of '74 gold ring ♪
♪ The eastern moon looks ready
for a wet kiss ♪
♪ To make the tide rise again ♪
♪ Moonlight ♪
♪ Feels right ♪
Hey!
♪ We'll see the sun come up
on Sunday morning ♪
♪ And watch it fade the moon
away ♪
♪ I guess you know
I'm giving you a warning ♪
♪ 'Cause me and moon
are itching to play ♪
♪ I'll take you on a trip
beside the ocean ♪
♪ And drop the top
at Chesapeake Bay ♪
♪ Ain't nothing like
a scattered dose of ocean ♪
♪ The moon will send you
on your way ♪
♪ Moonlight ♪
♪ Feels right ♪
-Hey.
Whoa.
I'm just playing. man.
-♪ Nights in white satin ♪
♪ Never reaching the end ♪
♪ Letters I've written ♪
♪ Never meaning to send ♪
♪ Beauty I've always missed ♪
♪ With these eyes before ♪
♪ Just what the truth is ♪
♪ I can't say any more ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
♪ Yes. I love you ♪
♪ Oh. how I love you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Gazing at people ♪
♪ Some hand in hand ♪
♪ Just what I'm going through ♪
♪ They can't understand ♪
♪ Some try to tell me ♪
♪ Thoughts they cannot defend ♪
♪ Just what you want to be ♪
♪ You will be in the end ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
♪ Yes. I love you ♪
♪ Oh. how I love you ♪
♪ Nights in white satin ♪
♪ Never reaching the end ♪
♪ Letters I've written ♪
♪ Never meaning to send ♪
♪ Beauty I've always missed ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
♪ Yes. I love you ♪
♪ Oh. how I love you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
♪ Yes. I love you ♪
♪ Oh. how I love you ♪
-♪ Lila came the day
I heard it thunder ♪
-♪ Lila ♪
-♪ There she was.
just a-standing by herself ♪
♪ When she came.
she brought me flowers ♪
♪ And. baby... ♪
Oh!
-Oh! Fuck!
Aah!
- Aah!
-Whoa.
-I loved her.
I loved her.
-I still do.
-♪ Dear friend.
if you want to feel better ♪
♪ Don't let the devil
make you toss this letter ♪
♪ If you've been crossed up
by hoodoo-voodoo ♪
♪ A wizard or the lizard ♪
♪ If you got family trouble.
man trouble. woman trouble ♪
♪ No light through the tunnel ♪
♪ If you're looking for
a true friend or a true lover ♪
♪ Or if you've been living
undercover ♪
♪ Well. I'm coming to your town
to break it all down ♪
♪ And help you
with all of this ♪
♪ I'm looking to help you
find bliss one day or one way ♪
♪ Can't miss ♪
♪ I'm here to tear all the walls
down ♪
♪ Doesn't matter if it's
a large town or a small town ♪
♪ Just like Joshua and
the fabled walls of Jericho ♪
♪ I'm here to tear down
the institution ♪
♪ God spoke to me.
said. "Listen to me ♪
♪ I anoint you with the power
that'll get 'em all movin'" ♪
♪ You're agitated.
you've prayed and meditated ♪
♪ You're concentrated
on getting elevated ♪
♪ By sundown Monday ♪
♪ You who come will be blessed
with a big money blessing ♪
♪ You will be doubted
by all the unbelievers ♪
♪ And all of the friends
I'm addressing ♪
♪ But you must tell
seven friends ♪
♪ You must first bring
♪ And don't be selfish
and keep this all to yourself ♪
♪ And don't eat shellfish ♪
♪ Hate is trying to take someone
else's love for yourself ♪
♪ But I'm here to tell you ♪
♪ That love is trying to help
someone else ♪
♪ I realize that you have tried
and tried ♪
♪ And are just about ready
to give up ♪
♪ But I got good news for you ♪
♪ God has spoken to my mind
and told me to tell you ♪
♪ To get moving in the right
direction for a change ♪
♪ I'm gonna put you
in the fast lane! ♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
♪ You need to see me
right away ♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
♪ You need to see me
right about now ♪
♪ God of Seven. open up
the windows of heaven ♪
♪ And pour out a rich
and mighty blessing ♪
♪ Not on his town or her town.
but your town ♪
♪ Are you ready
for the message? ♪
♪ I have a special
financial blessing ♪
♪ That once I have placed
in your hand ♪
♪ Yeah. I want you to begin
using this blessing ♪
♪ On the very first day
that you can ♪
♪ And if you are suffering
a strange sickness-ah ♪
♪ Or someone is blocking up
all of your success-ah ♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
Signed sincerely. yours
in faith. love. and peace.
your friend Archbishop
Harold Holmes.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm